Guide to the Nathaniel Moone photograph collection, 1889-1910 MS2115
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Nathaniel Moone photograph collection
1889-1910
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Moone, Nathaniel
MS2115
1 Linear Feet
Photographs were reproduced from 167 glass-plate negatives discovered by Mr. Moone in a townhouse on Fifth Street, NE, after the structure suffered a fire in 1977. The Gelman Library provided space for the first major exhibit of the photos in 1982. The identity of the photographer remains in question, but evidence indicates that they were likely taken by Frances Benjamin Johnston who was a well known photographer of Washington and its political figures during the period 1889-1910 and beyond. Many of the photos are of government officials during the McKinley and Roosevelt terms.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
The Special Collections Department at Gelman Library acquired the Nathaniel H. Moone Collection in 1995.
Historical or Biographical Note
Nathaniel Moone discovered 167 glass-plate negatives in a townhouse on Fifth Street, NE, after the structure suffered a fire in 1977.
Collection Scope and Content
The photographs were reproduced from 167 glass-plate negatives discovered by Mr. Moone in a townhouse on Fifth Street, NE, after the structure suffered a fire in 1977. The Gelman Library provided space for the first major exhibit of the photos in 1982. The identity of the photographer remains in question, but evidence indicates that they were likely taken by Frances Benjamin Johnston who was a well known photographer of Washington and its political figures during the period 1889-1910 and beyond. Many of the photos are of government officials during the McKinley and Roosevelt terms. An entire series consists of photos of the Lake Mohonk resort in Lake Mohonk, New York, which was a favorite retreat of President Theodore Roosevelt and other cultural elite during the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries. The collection consists of 168 photos. It is divided into six series: Maryland; Lake Mohonk, NY; Virginia; Washington, D.C.; Unidentified; and Portraits.
The Special Collections Department at Gelman Library acquired the Nathaniel H. Moone Collection in 1995.
Collection Organization
Organized into six series: Maryland; Lake Mohonk, NY; Virginia; Washington, D.C.; Unidentified; and Portraits.
Virginia; Mohonk Lake (N.Y.); Maryland; Washington (D.C.); Photographs; Johnston, Frances Benjamin; Moone, Nathaniel; McKinley, William; Roosevelt, Theodore
- Maryland, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 1; 1 Linear foot
  Scope and Contents note
  This series consists of photographs of bridges, churches, civil war monuments, and statues in Maryland.
  The materials range in date from 1889-1910.
  - Maryland, undated (Box 1)
    General note
  - Bridges--Burnside Bridge (Sharpsburg, MD), undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-11-PRI
  - Churches--Dunkard Church, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-16-PRI
  - Civil War Monuments--Antietam, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-12-PRI
  - Civil War Monuments--Antietam, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-13-PRI
  - Civil War Monuments--Antietam, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-14-PRI
  - Statues-- "Old Simon" (?, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-15-PRI
- Lake Mohonk, NY, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 2; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of photographs of resorts in Lake Mohonk, NY.
  - Lake Mohonk, N.Y., undated (Box 1)
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY), undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-59-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY), undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-65-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY)--Monuments, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-62-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY)--View of Gazebo, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-67-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY)--View of Gazebo and Hotel, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-60-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY)--View of Lake, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-61-PRI
  - Resorts--Lake Mohonk (NY)--Washington Profile House, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-66-PRI
- Virginia, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 3; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of photographs of Mount Vernon in Virginia. The materials range in date from 1889-1910.
  - Virginia, undated (Box 1)
  - Mount Vernon (VA)--Events--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-84-PRI
  - Mount Vernon (VA)--George Washington's Tomb, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-83-PRI
  - Mount Vernon (VA)--Portraits--Group, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-81-PRI
  - Mount Vernon (VA)--Portraits--Group, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-85-PRI
  - Mount Vernon (VA)--View from SE, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-82-PRI
- Washington, DC, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 4; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of photographs of aerial photographs, apartment houses, buildings, Capitol, dwellings, embassy buildings, events, galleries and museums, hotels, libraries, plazas, and White House in Washington, DC.
  - Washington, D.C., undated (Box 1)
  - Aerial Photographs--Bridges--The Long Bridge, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-102-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--NE view of Old Post Office and Capitol from Washington Monument, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-111-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--NE view of Old Post Office and Capitol from Washington Monument, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-112-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--Tidal Basin, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-101-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--View of Capitol from Washington Monument, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-109-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--View of Capitol from Washington Monument, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-110-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--View of Mall and city from Washington Monument, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-93-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--View of Washington Monument and White House from Cairo Hotel, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-103-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--View of Wyoming Apartments, above Connecticut Avenue and Columbia Road, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-86-PRI
  - Apartment Houses--The Concord, 1701 Oregon Avenue NW, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-89-PRI
  - Buildings--Public--Old Executive Office Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-100-PRI
  - Buildings--Public--Treasury--North Front Steps, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-87-PRI
  - Capitol--Rotunda--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-6-PRI
  - Capitol--Rotunda--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-7-PRI
  - Capitol--West Steps, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-8-PRI
  - Dwellings--Blaine, James G. Mansion, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-123-PRI
  - Dwellings--Blaine, James G. Mansion, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-124-PRI
  - Dwellings--Blaine, James G. Mansion, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-125-PRI
  - Dwellings--Blaine, James G. Mansion, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-126-PRI
  - Dwellings--Blaine, James G. Mansion, 2000 Massachusetts Avenue NW--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-127-PRI
  - Embassy Buildings--Mexican Legation--1413 I Street NW, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-58-PRI
  - Events--British Legation--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-34-PRI
  - Events--British Legation--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-56-PRI
  - Events--Capitol--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-75-PRI
  - Events--Capitol--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-76-PRI
  - Events--Capitol--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-77-PRI
  - Events--Capitol--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-78-PRI
  - Events--Capitol--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-79-PRI
  - Events--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey--Dewey's Commands "Capture or Destroy Montojo's Fleet", "When You Are Ready, Gridley, You May Fire May 1, 1898" in Lights on Marquee, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-73-PRI
  - Events--Parades--Civic Parade, 1899--Pennsylvania Avenue, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-70-PRI
  - Events--Parades--Civic Parade, 1899, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-71-PRI
  - Events--Parades--Civic Parade, 1899--Pennsylvania Avenue and 15th Streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-72-PRI
  - Events--Parades--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-74-PRI
  - Events--Parades--Homecoming for Admiral George Dewey, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-80-PRI
  - Events--White House--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-105-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-115-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-120-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-121-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Paintings--Ulysses S. Grant, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-116-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Paintings--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-117-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Paintings--Unidentified, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-118-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Statues--Napoleon Primo, undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-119-PRI
  - Galleries and Museums--Corcoran--Statues--Napoleon Primo, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-122-PRI
  - Graphic--Centennial Celebration Seal, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-152-PRI
  - Hotels--The Cairo Hotel, Q and 16th Streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-98-PRI
  - Hotels--The Cairo Hotel, Q and 16th Streets, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-99-PRI
  - Hotels--The Willard, Pennsylvania Avenue and 14th Street, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-95-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-3-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-4-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-5-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-53-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-54-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Main Reading Room (2), undated (Box 1, Folder 71)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-I-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Main Reading Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-2-PRI
  - Libraries--Library of Congress--Reading Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-47-PRI
  - Plazas--Dupont Circle--View of Women's National Democratic Club (Sarah Adams Whittemore House) and Leiter Mansion, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-113-PRI
  - Plazas--Farrugut Square, 17th and I Streets, NW, undated (Box 1, Folder 75)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-88-PRI
  - Plazas--Lafayette Square, undated (Box 1, Folder 76)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-108-PRI
  - Plazas--Scott Circle--16th Street and Massachusetts Avenue, NW, undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-104-PRI
  - White House--Communications Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-141-PRI
  - White House--Communications Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-142-PRI
  - White House--Gates, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-107-PRI
  - White House--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-96-PRI
  - White House--Interior, undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-156-PRI
- Unidentified, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 5; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of photographs of aerial photographs, buildings, camp, canals, cemeteries, conventions, docks, events, harbors, landscapes, and soldiers in unidentified places.
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 2)
  - Aerial Photographs--Dwellings--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-91-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--Dwellings--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-92-PRI
  - Aerial Photographs--Landscapes--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-64-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-35-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-36-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-37-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-38-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-39-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-40-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-41-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-42-PRI
  - Buildings--Industrial--Interior--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-43-PRI
  - Buildings--Military Academy--West Point (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-63-PRI
  - Camp--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-129-PRI
  - Camp--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-131-PRI
  - Camp--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-132-PRI
  - Canals--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-94-PRI
  - Canals--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-97-PRI
  - Cemeteries--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-25-PRI
  - Cemeteries--Monuments--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-9-PRI
  - Cemeteries--Statues--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-26-PRI
  - Cemeteries--Statues--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-27-PRI
  - Conventions--Political--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-32-PRI
  - Conventions--Political--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-33-PRI
  - Conventions--Political--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-162-PRI
  - Conventions--Political--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-163-PRI
  - Docks--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-69-PRI
  - Events--Daughters of the American Revolution Wreath, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-24-PRI
  - Events--Decorated Ballroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-49-PRI
  - Events--Decorated Ballroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-51-PRI
  - Events--Decorated Ballroom, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-52-PRI
  - Events--Decorated Dining Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-48-PRI
  - Events--Decorated Dining Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-50-PRI
  - Events--Flag-raising, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-13 7-PRI
  - Events--Flag-raising, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-138-PRI
  - Events--Flag-raising, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-139-PRI
  - Events--Flag-raising, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-140-PRI
  - Events--Military--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-21-PRI
  - Events--Military--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-22-PRI
  - Events--Military--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-165-PRI
  - Events--Military--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-166-PRI
  - Events--Red Cross--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-128-PRI
  - Events--Red Cross--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-133-PRI
  - Events--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-18-PRI
  - Events--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-19-PRI
  - Events--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-20-PRI
  - Events--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-106-PRI
  - Harbors--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-68-PRI
  - Landscapes--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-10-PRI
  - Landscapes--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-17-PRI
  - Soldiers--Spanish-American War (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-130-PRI
  - Soldiers--Spanish-American War (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-134-PRI
  - Soldiers--Spanish-American War (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-135-PRI
  - Soldiers--Spanish-American War (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-136-PRI
- Portraits, 1889-1910; MS2115 Series 6; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of photographs of portraits.
  - Portraits, undated (Box 2)
  - Portraits--Charles E. Smith, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-153-PRI
  - Portraits--Charles E. Smith, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-155-PRI
  - Portraits--Charles E. Smith, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-159-PRI
  - Portraits--Elihu Root, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-148-PRI
  - Portraits--Family--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-30-PRI
  - Portraits--Group--Bicyclists in front of Library of Congress, undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-114-PRI
  - Portraits--Group--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-57-PRI
  - Portraits--Group--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-90-PRI
  - Portraits--Group--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-164-PRI
  - Portraits--James D. Long, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-150-PRI
  - Portraits--James D. Long, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-157-PRI
  - Portraits--James D. Long, undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-158-PRI
  - Portraits--James Wilson (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-151-PRI
  - Portraits--James Wilson (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-154-PRI
  - Portraits--James Wilson (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-160-PRI
  - Portraits--James Wilson (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-161-PRI
  - Portraits--John Hay, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-143-PRI
  - Portraits--John Hay, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-144-PRI
  - Portraits--John Hay, undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-145-PRI
  - Portraits--Theodore Roosevelt (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-146-PRI
  - Portraits--Theodore Roosevelt (?), undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-147-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-23-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-28-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-29-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-3 I -PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-44-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-45-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-46-PRI
  - Portraits--Unidentified, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-55-PRI
  - Portraits--William McKinley, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
    [From original finding aid]: MC-149-PRI